madefire.com 2018-03-04

# Madefire, Inc.

                                            Madefire, Inc.
                                                Privacy Policy
Madefire, Inc. (“Madefire”) welcomes you to its website! Madefire values consumer privacy and is
committed both to safeguarding it and to protecting the information that you may provide to us. We want
to ensure that your experience with Madefire and our websites, mobile applications (“apps”) and other
products and services are as satisfying and safe as possible. We have established this Privacy Policy (the
"Privacy Policy") to explain how we collect, use and share information for your use of websites owned or
controlled by Madefire, apps or other products accessible through such websites (collectively, the
“Services”). Your use of the Services is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. By
accessing or using the Services, you agree to all of the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you
do not agree to such terms and conditions, please do not access or use the Services.
While you can access or use most of our Services for free, some of our Services are reserved for regis -
tered users. Registration is required to download certain apps and other software and also to receive on-
going communications from us. We do not require, as a condition of participation in any of our Services
or otherwise, that anyone disclose more information than is reasonably necessary for them to participate
in an activity.
This Privacy Policy will notify you of the following:
      1.  What personal information is collected and how it is collected;
      2.  The use of cookies and analytics;
      3.  Special note regarding children;
      4.  How the personal information collected is used;
      5.  With whom personal information may be shared;
      6.  What choices are available to you regarding the use of your personal information;
      7.  The security procedures in place to protect your personal information;
      8.  Click-through URL’s;
      9.  Interactive features;
      10. Submitting personal information
      11. Links and third party messaging;
      12. How you can ask questions, or send us comments, about this Privacy Policy;
      13. California privacy rights
      14. Safe Harbor statement; and
      15. Notice of changes to the Privacy Policy.
This Privacy Policy may change from time to time and your continued use of the Services constitutes
acceptance of such changes, so please check this Privacy Policy periodically for updates.
What Personal Information Is Collected and How Is it Collected
Personal information (also known as personally identifiable information) as used in this Privacy Policy is
information that directly identifies you and that may also be used to contact you either online or offline.
Madefire collect personal information on our websites and apps. Madefire may also collect personal
information in connection with marketing or email campaigns. The type of personal information collected
will vary depending upon the activity and may include your first and last name, e-mail address, account
information for certain third party sites or networks such as Facebook or Twitter, phone numbers
(including cell phone numbers), home address, and zip code. In addition, we may collect demographic
information such as gender; information about your computer, hardware, software and/or platform;
Internet IP address and connection; information about online activity such as website usage and time
spent on the Madefire website; and, other data that you may provide.
Cookies and Analytics

We use "cookies" in connection with the Services. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a website visitor's
hard drive to help us improve your access to our website and identify repeat visitors to our website. For
instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once,
thereby saving time while on our website. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personal
information on our website. The information that we collect with cookies may include your IP address,
information about how you interact with advertisements and other content, browser type, system type,
device type, the content and pages that you access, the date and time you view pages, and the page
from which you navigated.
In addition to cookies, we may use analytics tools and other third party technologies to collect non-
personal information in the form of various usage and user metrics when you use our online products and
services. These tools and technologies collect and analyze certain types of information, including cookies,
IP addresses, device and software identifiers, referring and exit URLs, onsite behavior and usage
information, app use metrics and statistics, feature use metrics and statistics, usage and purchase
history, MAC Address, mobile unique device ID, and/or other similar information. The third party analytics
companies who collect information on our websites, apps and other online products and/or services may
combine the information collected with other information they have independently collected from other
websites and/or apps or other online products and services relating to your activities across their network
of websites as well as apps and/or online products and services. Many of these companies collect and
use information under their own privacy policies. Some of these companies may also help us tailor
advertising that we think may be of interest to our users and to collect and use other data about user
activities on our services (e.g., to allow them to tailor ads on third party services). If you wish to not have
this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out as described below.
Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. To the extent we permit such
advertising to occur, you will continue to receive generic ads.
Special Note Regarding Children
We do not knowingly seek or collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen (13), nor
do we provide it to third parties. If we determine we have inadvertently gathered any personal information
from a user under the age of 13, we will promptly delete any and all such personal information from our
records.
How Personal Information is Used
We may use information from users of our websites, including personal information, behavioral metrics,
and other non-personally identifiable information to operate, provide, improve, and maintain our websites
and services, to develop new products and services, to prevent abuse and fraud, to personalize and
display advertisements and other content for you, and for other administrative and internal business
purposes. The personal information you provide us will allow you to access the Services and also allow
us to deliver messages to your personal accounts on certain third party sites or networks, such as
Facebook and Twitter. It will also be used to alert you of new products; handle and route your customer
service or technical support questions or issues; and, notify you of promotions, special events, and offers.
By providing us with a cell phone number, you agree that we may send you text messages either directly
or through a third party site or service (and you are responsible for any data rates or text fees that may
apply). We may also need to use your personal information to: (1) respond to subpoenas or court orders;
(2) establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; (3) protect ourselves, our
employees, contractors, customers, users and others and our Services from fraudulent, abusive, or
unlawful uses; (4) investigate and defend ourselves against third party claims or allegations; (5) enforce
our Terms of Use; or, (6) the extent otherwise required by applicable law. If you provide us account
information for a third-party service, such as Facebook or Twitter, we may also contact you on such third-
party service to provide information or updates about our Services.
This Privacy Policy is implemented pursuant to the framework of the U.S/EU Safe Harbor and the
U.S./Swiss Safe Harbor and adheres to the Safe Harbor privacy principles contained therein and
complies with the European Union Directive on Data Protection or the Federal Data Protection and
Information Commission of Switzerland.
If at any time you wish to opt-out from having your personal information used in order to deliver
information from Madefire about new products, services, or promotions, you may contact us at
support@madefire.com with the words “Opt Out” in the subject line of your email.

Sharing, Selling or Renting of Personal Information
We do not sell, rent, or give any retained customer information to third parties outside of what is
necessary to provide the Services. Such third parties have access to personal information needed to
perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. We may provide personal information to
third parties for their use in performing internal business functions (e.g., payment processing, customer
service, maintenance, security, data analysis, email transmission, beta testing, or data hosting) on our
behalf. Additionally, some third party service providers may collect information, including personal
information, on our behalf. Whenever possible, we require such third-parties to only collect and use
personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy, to maintain the confidentiality, security, and
integrity of such personal information, and for no purpose other than providing us with our requested
services.
In the event we are acquired by or merged with another company we may transfer your personal
information to the new company.
Your Access to and Control Over Your Personal Information
You may request that we modify or delete your user account(s) and any related data at any time. If you
wish to delete your user account(s), please email us at support@madefire.com with the words “Delete
Account” in the subject line of your email. You may, at any time, update or correct personal information
that you have provided to us by contacting us at the mailing or email address provided below.
How Is Personal Information Protected
The security of your personal information is important to us. We have implemented technical,
administrative and physical security measures to attempt to protect your personal information from
unauthorized access and improper use. However, please understand that no security measure is perfect
or impenetrable and therefore we cannot and do not guarantee the security of your personal information.
We also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific
job (for example, customer service) are granted access to personal information. The computers/servers in
which we store personal information are kept in a secure environment.
Click-through URLs.
In some of our email messages, we may use a "click-through URL" linked to content on a website. When
you click one of these URLs, you pass through a separate web server before arriving at the destination
page. We track this click-through data to help us determine interest in particular topics and measure the
effectiveness of our customer communications. If you prefer not to be tracked in this way, you should not
click text or graphic links in the email messages.
Interactive Features.
If you use a forum, blog, bulletin board, chat room, user commenting features, or other interactive or
social features that may be offered through any of our Services, you should be aware that any personal
information you submit, display, or publish there is considered publicly available and can be read,
collected, used, and disclosed by other users of those features, by us, and other third parties without
restriction. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us
at support@madefire.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in
which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.
Submitting Personal Information.
If you do not want to submit personal information that is necessary to provide or use a service or to fulfill
your request, you will not be able to access and/or participate in certain products and Services. For
example, you will not be able to register to received communications from us, or access and/or use
certain Madefire product features or online services. In addition, your refusal to submit personal
information may limit our ability to respond to your customer support inquiry in a timely fashion.
Links and Third Party Messaging
This website may contain links to other websites including social networking sites and services. Please
be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other websites. This
Privacy Policy does not apply to third party websites and we encourage our users to be aware when they
leave our website and to read the privacy statements of any other website that collects personal

information since your rights will be governed by those third party policies (and not by this Privacy Policy
or Madefire).
Additionally, when using the Services if you choose to download apps or other products you may be re-
directed to a third party site or service in order to complete the download. Those third party sites and
services may employ cookies. You may receive messages or other forms of communication in
connection with your use of the app or other products both from us and from third parties. Additionally,
your use of the app or other products is governed by and subject to the applicable terms of use and/or
privacy policy associated with the third party site or service, and we are not responsible for the content or
privacy practices of such other sites or services.
How You Can Ask Questions or Send Us Comments About This Privacy Policy
Madefire welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions about this
Privacy Policy or have technical or general support questions, please contact us at
support@madefire.com. You may also write to us at:
Madefire Inc.
805 Folger Ave.
Berkeley, CA, 94710
Telephone: (415) 273-9613
YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS
In addition to the rights set forth in this Privacy Policy, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits
California residents who are individual consumers or users of Madefire to request certain information
regarding its disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes.
Madefire has not and will not share your personal information with third parties for their direct marketing
purposes; accordingly, it will not maintain such a list of third parties. If you are a resident of California and
want additional information regarding how Madefire does not share your personal information with third
parties for their direct marketing purposes, you may contact us at support@madefire.com with the words
“California Privacy” in the subject line of your email.
Notice of Changes to the Privacy Policy
We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we do, we will update the “Last Updated” date at
the bottom of the Privacy Policy. If we make material changes to how we use personal information, we will
attempt to notify you of the change and to give you the opportunity to exercise choice as to how your
personal information is used. For all changes to this Privacy Policy, we will post the updated Privacy
Policy on our website. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy periodically to stay informed about
our collection, use and disclosure of personal information. Your continued use of the Services covered by
this Privacy Policy constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates.
Last Updated: December 27, 2012
